Toni Morrison Papers, 1908-2017: Finding Aid C1491
mss EADs that duplicate ones in Manuscripts
- Writings, 1917-2017 April 11; 94 boxes; 16 items
  - Speeches and Lectures, 1975 May 30-2015 October 1; 8 boxes
    - Nina Simone Tribute, 2004 June 21; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 20)
      Delivered at Sing the Truth: A Tribute to Nina Simone, JVC Jazz Festival, Carnegie Hall.
    - "Books, Politics, and the Culture War", 2004 July 26; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 21)
      Delivered at the Progressive Book Club Panel, Boston MA.
    - "The War on Error (in a Reign of Error)", 2004 August 29; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 22)
      Delivered at Amnesty International, Edinburgh, Scotland.
    - Amy Gutmann Inauguration Speech, 2004 October 14; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 23)
    - Romare Bearden Tribute, 2004 October 16; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 24)
      New York City.
    - Academy of Culture Remarks, 2004 November 9; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 25)
    - "The Future of Humanities in a Fragmented World", 2004 December 28; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 26)
      Delivered at an MLA panel and later published in PMLA.
    - Angela Brown Introduction, circa 2005; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 27)
    - Notes on Parenting, 2005 March 14; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 28)
      Metro Parents Detroit.
    - "Civil Society and World Governance", 2005 March 30; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 29)
      International Civil Society Conference, Columbia University.
    - "Overdue: A Writer's Debt; A Reader's Interest", 2005 April 3; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 30)
      Friends of Princeton University Library.
    - Atelier Fundraiser Remarks, 2005 April 16; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 31)
    - Leon Forrest Lecture, 2005 May 2; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 32)
      Delivered at Northwestern University.
    - Opera America Keynote, 2005 May 5; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 33)
      Detroit.
    - Ramapo College Commencement Address, 2005 May 25; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 34)
    - Princeton Baccalaureate Address, 2005 May 29; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - Aspen Institute Speech, 2005 July 8; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - University of Miami Fall Convocation, 2005 August 30; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 3)
      Robert & Judi Prokop Newman Lecture.
    - Peter Sellars Introduction, 2005 September 29; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 4)
      Gish Award Presentation.
    - Russell Banks Introduction, 2005 October 28; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 5)
      Delivered at the Princeton Public Library.
    - Norman Mailer Introduction, 2005 November 16; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 6)
      Delivered at the National Book Foundation, New York City.
    - Princeton Trustee's Dinner Remarks, 2006 January 26; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 7)
    - Shippenburg University Speech, 2006 February 23; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 8)
    - New York Historical Society Lecture, 2006 March 3; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 9)
    - North American Network of Cities of Asylum Speech, 2006 April 6; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 10)
      Las Vegas.
    - Opera Clubs of America Speech, 2006 April 19; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 11)
    - Macalester College Convocation and Inaguration of the Institute of Global Citizenship, 2006 September 5; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 12)
      St. Paul, Minnesota.
    - "The Foreigner's Home", 2006 November 6; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 13)
      Delivered at the Louvre.
    - Slam Poetry Introduction, 2006 November 10; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 14)
      Paris.
    - "Harlem on My Mind", 2006 November 15; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 15)
    - "Art is Otherwise", 2007 March 5; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 16)
      Delivered at the Baryshnikov Arts Centre, New York City.
    - President's Retreat on the Creative & Performing Arts Remarks, 2007 April 19; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 17)
    - Radcliffe Medal Acceptance, 2007 June 8; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 18)
    - Vicky Colbert Introduction, 2007 September 27; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 19)
      Delivered at the Clinton Global Initiative Award Ceremony.
    - Toni Morrison Elementary School Dedication, 2007 October 7; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 20)
      Delivered in Lorain, Ohio.
    - Tracie Luck Introduction, 2007 November 9; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 21)
    - Obama Fundraiser Remarks, 2008 February 23; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 22)
      Delivered at the Paula Cooper Gallery, New York City.
    - Princeton Campaign Remarks, 2008 April 3; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 23)
      Delivered in New York City.
    - "Peril", 2008 April 28; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 24)
      Remarks upon the receipt of the 2008 PEN/Borders Literary Service Award; later published as an essary in Burn This Book: PEN Writers Speak Out on the Power of the Word.
    - National Conference of Boards of Education Remarks, 2009 April 5; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 25)
      Delivered in San Diego, California.
    - "Home", 2009 April 23; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 26)
      Oberlin College Convocation.
    - Seamus Heaney Introduction, 2009 April 28; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 27)
      Delivered at the Princeton Poetry Festival.
    - Toby Devan Lewis, 2010 April 16; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 28)
      ArtTable Award, New York City.
    - ALA Convention Speech, 2010 June 26; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 29)
      Washington, D.C.
    - Gish Prize Chinua Achebe, 2010 October 27; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 30)
      Delivered on Toni Morrison's behalf in New York City.
    - "Invisible Ink: Reading the Writing, Writing the Reading", 2011 March 1; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 31)
      Wilson College Signature Lecture Series, Princeton University.
    - Feminist Legal Theory Conference Speech, 2011 March 30; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 32)
      Delivered at the University of Baltimore.
    - "The Past is Now", 2011 April 8; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 33)
      Delivered at the University of Connecticut conference "Understanding the Past, Transforming the Future."
    - Rutgers Commencement Address, 2011 May 15; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 34)
    - University of Geneva Honorary Doctorate Acceptance Speech, 2011 October 14; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 35)
    - Sackler Center First Award Acceptance Speech, 2012 April 18; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 36)
    - Centennial Medal Presentation to Peter Sellars, 2012 April 25; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 37)
      Delivered at the American Academy in Rome gala dinner at the Plaza Hotel.
    - Rush Holt Fundraiser Remarks, 2012 October 8; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - Writers Celebration of Romare Beardon Remarks, 2012 December 3; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 2)
      Delivered at the 92nd St. Y, read on Toni Morrison's behalf.
    - "Goodness: Altruism and the Literary Imagination", 2012 December 6; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 3)
      Ingersoll Lecture, Harvard Divinity School.
    - "The Price of Wealth; the Cost of Care", 2013 May 9; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 4)
      Nichols-Chancellor's Medal, Vanderbilt University.
    - Maya Angelou Tribute, 2013 November 20; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 5)
      Delivered at the National Book Awards.
    - Amiri Baraka Tribute, 2014 April 8; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 6)
      Delivered at the AAAL meeting.
    - Salman Rushdie Introduction, 2014 May 5; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 7)
      Delivered at the PEN Gala.
    - Jessye Norman Tribute, 2014 November 21; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 8)
      Delivered at the Metropolitan Guild Luncheon, New York City.
    - National Book Critic's Circle Remarks, 2015 March 12; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 9)
    - Knopf 100th Anniversary Remarks, 2015 October 1; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 10)
      Delivered at the New York Public Library.
    - Unidentified Speech Fragments, undated; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 11)
  - Personal and Miscellaneous Writings, 1958-2012; 2 boxes
    Includes journal entries and autobiographical writing, as well as drafts of letters and miscellaneous notes.
    This material is grouped by type.
    - Biographical Notes, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 1)
    - Journal Entries, 1958-2005; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1997-2012; 2 boxes
      Notebooks include a variety of material, including material relating to writings and lectures, correspondence drafts, and other unrelated notes.
      - Legal pad 1, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 3)
        Includes letter drafts to Nellie McKay, Chris Eisgruber, Sue Devine, Judith Herrin, and Oprah Winfrey.
      - Legal pad 2, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 4)
        Includes letter drafts to Carma Hinton, Gloria Smart, and John Wideman; and notes for the Louvre.
      - Legal pad 3, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 5)
      - Legal pad 4, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 6)
      - Legal pad 5, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 7)
      - Legal pad 6, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 8)
      - Legal pad 7, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 9)
        Includes drafts of article for Le Monde, Grendel and His Mother, and The Dead of September 11.
      - Legal pad 8, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 10)
      - Legal pad 9, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 11)
      - Legal pad 10, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 12)
      - Legal pad 11, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 13)
      - Marie Papier Notebooks, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous Notes, undated; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 15)
      - PEN World Voices Notebook, circa 2012; 1 folder (Box 320, Folder 1)
        Includes miscellaneous notes, including notes for Home and Desdemona, lists and contacts, drafts of letters, and essay or lecture outlines.
      - Dearly Beloveds Notebook, circa 1997; 1 folder (Box 320, Folder 2)
        Mostly blank notebook that includes some notes on the "She Wolf."
  - Miscellaneous Writings and Notes, 2017 April 11; AM 2018-78; 1 folder (Box 326, Folder 3)
    Includes two small notepads and a loose sheet.
- Correspondence, 1953-2018 January; 41 boxes
  This series is arranged alphabetically by last name.
  Consists primarily of personal correspondence from friends, family, and colleagues. Professional correspondence and fan mail can be found in Morrison's office working files.
  - 70th Birthday Cards, 2001; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - 75th Birthday Guest Book, 2006; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - 80th Birthday Cards, 2011; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - A, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 67, Folder 4-5)
  - A, 2010-2017; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 30)
  - Abinader, Elmaz, 1986-1990; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Achebe, Chinua, 1991-2005; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Achebe, Chinua, undated; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 41)
  - Adams, Eve, 2004-2007; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Adero, Malaika, 1996-2007; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Ahearn, Eileen, 1979-2008; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Al Abdullah, Queen Raina, 2004; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Allen, Danielle, 2002-2013; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Allende, Isabel, 1987-2001; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Al Muhammad, Princess Firyal, 2013; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Als, Hilton, 2000-2003; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Annan, Kofi and Nane, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Angelou, Maya, 1994-2013; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Appiah, Anthony, 1990; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Asaro, Sal, 1997-2009; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Atanasoff, Jeanne, 1988-2015; 2 folders (Box 68, Folder 11-12)
    Includes photographs.
  - Atlas, James, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - B, 1985-2015; 3 folders (Box 69, Folder 1-3)
  - B, 2011-2017; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 31)
  - Bach, Jean, 1992; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Bailey, Donna, 1982-2009; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Baker, Houston and Charlotte, 1987-1992; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Baldwin, Emma Berdis Jones, 1977-1999; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Baldwin, James, 1976, 1986; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Bambara, Toni Cade, 1977-1995; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Bambara, Toni Cade, 1977-1995; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Banfield, Bill, 2002; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Banks, Russell, 1990-2002; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Baraka, Amiri and Amina, 1981-2004; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Batton, Susan Sayre, 1990-1994; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Belafonte, Harry, 1990; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Bell, Derrick, 1990-1996; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Benham, Joan A., 1999-2001; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Berg, Joel, 1982-2016; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Berg, Joel, 2008; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 9)
  - Bergman, Robert and Laurie McCannel, 1997-2010; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Bergman, Robert and Laurie McCannel, 2016-2017; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 14)
  - Bernstein, Robert L., 1988-2002; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Bertolino, James, 1983; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Bezos, Mackenzie Tuttle, 1990-2014; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Bezos, Jeff and Mackenzie, 2011; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 18)
  - Bhabha, Homi, 1994-2011; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Bonetti, Kay, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Bourgois, Christian and Dominique, 1988-2000; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Bowen, William, 1987-1998; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Boyle, Kay, 1984-1987; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Bracey, Phyllis Woods, 1988-2003; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Includes a photograph.
  - Bradley, Bill, 1994-1996; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Breitwieser, Mitch, 1988-1991; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Brodsky, Claudia, 1990-2015; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Brombert, Beth and Victor, 1989-2008; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Brombert, Beth and Victor, 2002; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 15)
  - Brony, Elizabeth, 1995-1997; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Brooks, Cynthia, 1999; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Brooks, Georgia, 1971-2011; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Brooks, Gwendolyn, 1993-1997; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Brooks, Lois Wofford, 1982-2006; 2 folders (Box 71, Folder 13-14)
  - Brooks, Lois Wofford, 1982-2006; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Brown, Carlene, 1977-2012; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Brown, Clarence, 2013; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Brown, Carlene and Clarence, 2010; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 5)
  - Bruckner, Carol, undated; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Bruckner, Carol, 2011; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 10)
  - Bush, Barbara, 1989; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Busia, Abena, 1985-2011; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Byatt, A.S., 1994-2001; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - C, 1977-2015; 2 folders (Box 72, Folder 7-8)
  - C, 1997-2014; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 32)
  - Cammerzell, Frederick, 1988-2008; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Caro, Robert, 1993; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Carpenter, Lea, 2003-2013; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Carpenter, Lea, 2012; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 31)
  - Carrasco, Davíd, 1991-2013; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Carrasco, Davíd, 1996; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 36)
  - Carroll, Doris, 1980-1995; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Carter, Graydon, 2001-2011; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Carter, Rosalynn and Jimmy, 1980-2009; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Carter, Rosalynn and Jimmy, 1980-2009; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 7)
    holiday card
  - Casebere, James, 2008-2012; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Cepeda, Patricia, 1998-2000; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Champ, Norman B., 1987-1992; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Cheatwood, Kiarri T-H., 1981-1989; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Cheever, Susan, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Cisneros, Sandra, 1998 January 20; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Clark, Ana Steele and John, 1986-2011; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Clark, Ana Steele and John, undated; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 24)
  - Clark, Larry, 1986; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Clemons, Dolores, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Clinton, Bill and Hillary, 1993-2006; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Clinton, Bill and Hillary, White House Christmas Card, 1998; 1 folder (Box 266, Folder 14)
    An oversize Christmas card from the Clintons dated 1998 can be found with other posters and oversize memorabilia.
  - Clinton, Bill and Hillary, White House Invitations, 1993-2000; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Clinton, Bill and Hillary, Holiday Cards, 1996-1998; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 4)
  - Coetzee, J.M., 2004; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Cole, Johnetta B., 1995; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Conarroe, Joel, 2005; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Conner, Marc, 2001-2005; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Cook, Beverly and Charles, 1988-1993; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Cooper, Bill, Clarissa, Ashley and Courtney, 2003; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Cornell, Drucilla, 1993-2007; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Cosby, Bill and Camille, 1986-1997; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Cosby, Camille, 1994-2011; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 8)
  - Couric, Katie, 2012; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Curasi, Anne, 2009-2015; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - D, 1970-2012; 2 folders (Box 74, Folder 12-13)
  - D, 2011-2017; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 33)
  - d'Amboise, Jacques, 1987-2012; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Daniel, Clifton, 1983; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Danielpour, Richard, 2002-2007; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Danticat, Edwidge, 2014; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Davis, Eisa, 2005-2011; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Davis, Natalie Zemon, 1992-2013; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Davis, Thadious, 1998; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Dee, Ruby and Ossie Davis, 1992-2012; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Dee, Ruby and Ossie Davis, undated; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 38)
  - Dees, Morris, 2004; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - DeCrow, Karen, 1988-2006; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Demme, Jonathan, 1997-1999; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Denard, Carolyn, 1991-2015; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Denard, Carolyn, 2015-2017; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - DiFilippo, Rosemary, 1991-2014; 2 folders (Box 75, Folder 6-7)
  - DiFilippo, Rosemary, 2011; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 14)
  - Dimock, Peter, 1985-2010; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Dimock, Wai-Chee, 1985-1994; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Dinkins, David and Joyce, 1989-2007; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Dinkins, Joyce, 2011; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 6)
  - Dixon, Melvin, 1977-1987; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Doctorow, E.L., 1995-2001; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Dorfman, Ariel, 1986-2002; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Dorris, Michael and Louise Erdrich, 1985-1993; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Dubois, Laurent, 1992-2005; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - E, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - E, 2016; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 34)
  - Eisgruber, Chris, 2017; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 26)
  - Elias, Robert and Helen, 1953-2013; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Ellison, Ralph and Fanny, undated; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - English, Lady Judith, 2005; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Epstein, Barbara, 2000; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Epstein, Jason, 1996-2003; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Epstein, Jason, 2011; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 16)
  - F, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 76, Folder 14-15)
  - F, 1994-2017; 1 folder (Box 329, Folder 1)
  - Fabre, Geneviève, 1992-2007; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Fagles, Robert and Lynne, 1994-2008; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Farrow, Mia, 1995-1997; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Faust, Drew, 2001-2016; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Faust, Drew, undated; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 11)
  - Featherston, Natalie, 2004-2010; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Ferris, William, 1997-2009; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Fishkin, Shelley Fisher, 1992-2000; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Florio, Jim, 1993; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Forbes, Sheila, undated; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Forrest, Leon and Anne, 1998; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Foster, Jodie, 1985-1993; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1986-1992; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Frederick, Wayne I. A., 2016; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Frederick, Wayne I.A., 2017; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 32)
  - Freedgood, Anne, 1980-1994; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Freedgood, Julia, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Frelinghuysen, Barrett, 2000-2013; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Freund, Gerald, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Fulmer, Jackie, 1997-2003; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Fultz, Lucille, 1989-2016; 2 folders (Box 77, Folder 11-12)
  - Fultz, Lucille, 2017; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 22)
  - G, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 77, Folder 13-14)
  - G, 2011-2017; 1 folder (Box 329, Folder 2)
  - Gaines, Kevin, 1994; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Gass, William, 1985-1993; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Gates, Henry Louis, 1983-2008; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Gates, Henry Louis, 2011; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 15)
  - Gerzina, Gretchen Holbrook, 1986-2007; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Giddings, Paula, 1974-2009; 2 folders (Box 78, Folder 5-6)
  - Gilbert, Sandra, 1989-2005; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Ginsburg, Rachel and Philip, 1989-2012; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Giovanni, Nikki, 1989-2016; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Giovanni, Nikki, 2018 January; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 5)
  - Glasser, Barbara, 1988-2010; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Goellner, Ellen, 1992-2015; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Goerner, Lee, circa 1987-1992; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Goheen, Margaret and Robert, 1988-2008; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Gordimer, Nadine, 1985-2002; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Gornick, Vivian, 1990; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Graham, Billy, 2000-2011; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Graham, Maryemma, 2005-2015; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Grant, Alice, 1984-2003; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Grauer, Rhoda, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Greaves, William, 1988-2005; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Gregorian, Vartan, 1987-2012; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Griffin, Farah Jasmine, 2003-2016; 2 folders (Box 79, Folder 7-8)
  - Griffin, Farah Jasmine, 2011-2017; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 1)
  - Grosvenor, Vertamae, 1979-1994; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Groth, Patricia, 1985-1995; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Gubar, Susan, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Guénif-Souilamas, Nacira, 2007; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Gunn, Bill, 1984; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Gutmann, Amy, 2000-2012; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Gutmann, Amy, 2016-2017; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 19)
  - H, 1970-2015; 2 folders (Box 79, Folder 15-16)
  - H, 2004-2017; 1 folder (Box 329, Folder 3)
  - Haba, Jim and Erica, 1998-2007; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Haba, Jim and Erica, undated; 1 folder (Box 328, Folder 7)
  - Hale, Janet Campbell, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Harper, Conrad and Marsha, 1987-2008; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Harper, Michael S., 1975-2003; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Haskell, Molly, 1987-1994; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Hayes, Jennifer and Graham, 1996-2011; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Heaney, Seamus, 1996-1998; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Heiskell, Andrew, 1986-1996; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Hendricks, Obery, 2002-2014; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Herrin, Judith, 1992-1995; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Hickey, Meghan, 1996-2004; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Higginbotham, Jr., A. Leon, 1978-1998; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Hinton, William, 1984-1999; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Hodsoll, Frank, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Holbrook, Hal, 2014; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Holt, Rush, 2012; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - hooks, bell, 1997; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Hoppenthaler, John, 2000; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Hoppenthaler, John, 2011; 1 folder (Box 327, Folder 28)
  - Houston, Pam, 2003-2006; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 19)